Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Fair Trade, 1988-2012; Series 2
  - Bananas, 1988-2011; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Chiquita-Honduras, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Costa Rica Banana Industry, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dole-banana investigation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Marciana Funez Benefit Fund/Belize Bananas, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "The Truth about Bananas" information and activity pack, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Thank you Postcards-Dole Food Inc., undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - USFT Empowerment Banana, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Eskimo Banana Plantation, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Foro Emaus-Banana Enclave, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Chiquita Clippings, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Del Monte-Banana Research, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Bananas-Class Action Suit, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Don Weiner-Campaign, Chiquita, 1993-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Chiquita-Robert Kistinger, 1994-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Del Monte, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Bananas Lawsuit-DBCP, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Fair Trade Banana Bulletins, 1995-1997; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - New York Times-banana/Europe, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Banana Consumption reports, 1996-1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Euroban Banana campaign prerp, 1996-1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Banana and Society-annotated bibliography, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Banana Press-The New York Times, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Banana Linkreports and updates, 1997-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Euroban Meeting-November 1997 Gelnhausen [1], Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Euroban Meeting-February 1998, Medingen [2], Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Euroban Meeting-September 1999, Bonn [3], Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Fair Trade Bananas [1], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Fair Trade Bananas [2], 2004; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Fresh Del Monte Produce research, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - The Banana Chain, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Bananas/Environmental groups, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - BanaFair, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Bananas for the World-Costa Rica, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Bananas-Global and Regional Trade, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Bananas/Government of Guatemala, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Banana Industry, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Banana Industry in the Windward Islands, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Bananas Press, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Banana Project Budget, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Banana Notes and memos-Bob Perillo, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Bananas-Sustainable Consumption, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Banana Task Force, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Banana Updates/alerts, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Bananas/USTR, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Banana Workers Tour, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Chiquita, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Chiquita assorted emails, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Chiquita-Arizona and Alabama, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Chiquita-Bananas, GNIB article, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Chiquita-campaign meeting, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Chiquita campaign notes, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Chiquita campaign resource, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Chiquita campaign research, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Chiquita-Carl Linder, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Chiquita/Colsiba correspondence, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Chiquita/Colsiba Guatemala meeting, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Chiquita correspondence, 1998-2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Chiquita Factsheets, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Chiquita Initiative, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Chiquita-Journalist Lists, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Chiquita/Oxfam Canada, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Chiquita-Panama, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Chiquita Press Events, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Chiquita Research-Wiener, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Chiquita-Revelations, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Chiquita Shareholders, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Chiquita "sign-on" letter, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Chiquita Strategic Planning Meeting, Honduras, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Chiquita-Cincinnati Enquirer [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Chiquita-Cincinnati Enquirer [2], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Chiquita-Cincinnati Enquirer-Wednesday, May 6, 1998 [1], Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Chiquita-Cincinnati Enquirer-Sunday, May 3, 1998 [2], Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Chiquita Response to Cincinnati Enquirer [3], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Chiquita-Cincinnati Enquirer Trial articles [4], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Chiquita report, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Cincinnati Labor/Chiquita, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Caribbean Congress of Labor/Colsiba, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Cosibah [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Cosibah-Honduras [2], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Costa Rican Banana Industry, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Costa Rica and Panama Banana Trip Report, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Costa Rica Update, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Del Monte-California, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Dole Clippings, 1998-2003; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Emaus Forum, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Euroban/Chiquita, 1998-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Euroban Working Group-Chiquita, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Foro Emaus-"Bananas for the World and the Negative Consequences for Costa Rica?", 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - The Fresh Del Monte Story: Global Shenanigans in Fresh Fruits and Vegetables, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Global Exchange Bananas, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala-Del Monte [1], 1998-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala-Del Monte [2], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Hurricane Mitch, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hurricane Mitch, Bananas, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hurricane Mitch, Dole, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Hurricane Mitch, Chiquita, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hurricane Mitch Relief, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Hurricane Mitch/scorecard, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - International Banana Agreement, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - International Banana Conference [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - International Banana charter draft [2], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - International Banana Conference preparation materials [3], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - IUF and Bananas, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Marion Traub-Werner, Interviews (Chiquita), 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Pesticide Action Network, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Sitrabi-Correspondence, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - UFCW proposal, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - UK Bananas, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - World Development Movement, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - World Trade Organization-Bananas [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - World Trade Organization-Bananas [2], 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - World Trade Organization AFL-CIO [3], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - World Trade Organization rulings/press [4], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Alistair Smith, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Alistair Smith, Chiquita, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Banana Alert, Chiquita, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Banana Crisis, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Bananas, Ecuador-Steve Striffler, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Banana Interviews, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bananas-ILWU/ILA, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Banana import data, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Banana Link correspondence, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Bananas-market shares, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Banana meetings in Washington DC, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Banana plannings, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Banana Study [1], 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Banana Study: Anne-Claire Chambron [2], 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Banana Summit, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Bananas, Toronto, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Banana Trade News Bulletins, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Banana Trade Statistics, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Bill Clinton's California/Mexico Trip, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Chiquita, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Chiquita Annual Report and Form 10-K, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Chiquita-campaign strategy, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Chiquita-Costa Rica, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Chiquita-Colsiba, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Chiquita Communications, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Chiquita and Del Monte updates and information, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Chiquita Fashion Show, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chiquita-Hurricane Mitch, Honduras, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chiquita-LAWG, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Chiquita loss, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Chiquita Stock/shareholders meeting, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Colsiba Strategy meeting-Costa Rica, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Colsiba Conference, Nicaragua, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Colsiba Crisis Strategy, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Colsiba Booklet, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Costa Rica Bananas, 1999-2004; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Costa Rica SA8000, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Costa Rica Banana Crisis, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Del Monte, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Del Monte alerts and updates, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Del Monte-Bandegua intimidation, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Del Monte: Brazil, Uruguay, Chile, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Del Monte, Don Wiener, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Del Monte, European actions, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Del Monte-Florida Rally, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Del Monte-Fresh Cut Fruit, Inc. and Handi-Pak Food, Inc., 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Del Monte-ILO, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Del Monte, IUF, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Del Monte investors, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Del Monte, John J. Sweeney, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Del Monte-Miami, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Del Monte negotiations, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Del Monte-Morales Region, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Del Monte-State of Wisconsin Investment Board, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Del Monte Workers, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Del Monte, Richard G. Wolford, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Del Monte-Sitrabi, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Del Monte and WI Investment board, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Dole/COSBA/UNSI, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Dole-form 10K for fiscal year 1999, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ecuador Banana Research, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ecuador Trip, bananas, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - European Union "first come, first served," proposal, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Fresh Del Monte business information report, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Fresh Del Monte correspondence, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Fresh Del Monte, Form 20-F, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Fresh Del Monte Form 20-F (2), 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Fresh Del Monte market analysis, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Fresh Del Monte Produce "Fresh Facts", 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Fresh Del Monte Research Notes, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization, bananas, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Guatemala-USTR Sitrabi, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Hazel Ross-Robinson and Associates, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Hurricane Mitch in Nicaragua, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Hurricane Mitch, Rollbacks, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - The International Banana Trade, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - International Development Bureau Consultative Group-Stockholm Meeting, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - IUF Banana Working Group, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Latin American Working Group-Chiquita, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - The New Internationalist, the Big Banana Split, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - The Packer-banana news, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Post-Hurricane Mitch Legislation and Relief, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Post-Hurricane Mitch-OTR, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Sitrabi, Del Monte, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Sitrabi/Fresh Del Monte campaign, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Sitrabi reports, information, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Sitraterco/African Palms, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Sitraterco-Honduras, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Sitrap/Del Monte, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Socail Audits and the Banana Industry in Costa Rica, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Sopisco News, Week 47/99-Week 16/00, 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Supermarkets-Company profiles, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Rainforest Alliance/Chiquita [1], 1999-2003; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Rainforest Alliance/Chiquita [2], 2005; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - RWA proposal/Regional Agreement, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Winward Islandward Island farmers (WINFA), 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Adelien van de Kastelle correspondence, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - A Strategic Analysis of the Central American Banana Industry: an Industry in Crisis, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - "A Strategic Analysis of the Central American Banana Industry" Display Copy, September 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Bananas-Correspondence, 2000-2007; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Banana Study [1], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Banana Study: Country and regional reports [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Banana Study: Regional Analysis [3], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Banana Strategies and reports, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Banana Work-Ecuador and Guatemala, 2000-2002; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Banana Workshop, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Banana Workers Bulletin, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Bibliography-bananas, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Bob Perillo Banana Report, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Chiquita Annual Report and Form 10-K, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Chiquita Brands International, Inc. -Corporate Responsibility Report, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Chiquita Code of Conduct, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Chiquita-Costa Rica, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Chiquita/Colsiba/Miami, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Chiquita clippings, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Chiquita company information, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Chiquita Corporate Responsibility Report [1], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Chiquita Corporate Responsibility Report [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Chiquita-Corporate Responsibility Report [3], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Chiquita Notice to Shareholders, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Chiquta-Jeff Zalla, 2000-2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Chiquita releases, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Chiquita 10-K, 2000-2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Coverco Report-"Coffee Workers in Guatemala", 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Codes of Conduct Updates; SA 8000, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Del Monte Agreement, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Del Monte-Kenya, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Dole Proxy Statement, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Dole SUTRAFSCO, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Del Monte-State Department, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Dole in Ecuador, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Dole Food Company information, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Euroban Meeting-January 2000, Paris, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Euroban Meeting correspondence, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Expense Accounts, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Fresh Del Monte company information, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Fresh Del Monte expansion, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala Ports, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Honduras Banana Crisis, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - International Banana Agreement, 2000-2005; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - IUF/Colsiba Seminar, Miami, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - IUF/Colsiba, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - MacArthur Foundation proposal, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Nicaragua-PRESITEX, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sitrabi-bananas, 2000-2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Sitrabi/Colsiba banana correspondence, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Union labels, 2000-2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 2001: Beyond Banana Boom-and-Bust, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Banana Industry, 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Banana Industry Overview, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Banana Trade News Bulletin-No.24, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Big Three Banana Companies Summary, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Chiquita-Honduras, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Chiquita-Jeff Zalla, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Chiquita Corporate Responsibility Report, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Chiquita/Dole/Noboa, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Chiquita/Solidarity Center presentation, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Chiquita and IUF/Colsiba agreement [1], 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Chiquita and IUF/Colsiba agreement [2], 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Colombia Banana Study, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Colsiba Funding Meeting, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Colsiba/First Come, First Serve, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Colsiba Strategic Plan, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Dole Communications, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Dole Campaign, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Dole Campaign/Colsiba, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Dole Campaign Strategy discussions, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Dole Sign-on letter drafts, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Dole sign-on letter drafts (2), 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Ecuador bananas- Human Rights Watch Report, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Ecuador "Plan Colombia", 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - European Comission Contact information, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Euroban Meeting, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)